oo I hope you enjoy this banana noodle
Curry food demo from my big banana book
part of the ultimate raw vegan bundle
welcome welcome welcome we're going to
do a banana Curry food demo for the
ultimate raw vegan bundle I'm wearing my
rayb band meta so that I can go hands
free and be making this recipe so you
can see exactly what I'm seeing hey
Erica hey Denny hey everyone welcome
welcome we're going to be doing a banana
Curry food demo it's from my uh banana
Commander's big banana book oh oh hey
hey great to see you everyone flooding
in I love it I love it I hope you're
ready for something sweet and savory
this is one of my favorite new recipes
for my big banana book is a part of the
ultimate raw vegan bundle I'm actually
going to post this is the first time
I've ever done this I'm going to post my
link in here and uh pin it if I can
figure that out let's see come on how do
I pin that sucker pin comment there we
go so that's pinned there if anyone
wants to check out the bundle that
hasn't it is ridiculous it is over 33
there's 33 not over 33 raw vegan and
lifestyle contributions to this bundle
worth over 840 bucks for just $50 but
only for a limited time I'm going to see
if I can set you up here that's not a
good place actually cuz I need that bowl
at some point let's see welcome welcome
welcome if you guys have any questions
you can let me know and otherwise I'm
going to switch to the glasses view here
pretty quick and again I just want to
let you know this is a part of the
ultimate raw vegan bundle uh celebration
and it's part of my big banana book I
have that book here so I can look at the
recipes and when we switch to this view
you'll be able to see that as well if
you guys have any questions you can ask
me and I can click here and I can even
hear them in my ear it's pretty darn
cool but this is going to be my dinner I
love bananas obviously with my banana
mustache my banana shirt and being known
as the banana Commander so I created the
big banana book it's got uh what is it
40 over 40 I think it's 43 but over 40
banana based recipes that are among my
favorite of all time from sweet simple
ones you know smoothies and cereals I'm
going to be doing actually a Serial demo
near the end of the bundle here which I
hope you want to check out it's called
the real fro Loops it's really darn good
uh to a little bit more fancy ones and
splits and a whole bunch of other fun
stuff uh I also have a float which I'll
be doing a food demo of later in the
week as well and then there's just a ton
of banana information in there cuz
there's a lot of misinformation about
bananas people afraid of bananas or
thinking because they're seedless that
they're bad and GMO and man-made and you
know worried about the ecological
footprint and all that stuff and I
wanted to dispel myths you know to me
bananas are like the rice and beans or
rice and bread of the raw food movement
uh they're an amazing staple food
inexpensive available year round
delicious satisfying hello hello welcome
welcome and very soon we're going to get
into one of the Savory recipes from the
book because yeah bananas for lunch is
great you know and sometimes I make
bananas for dinner just a banana
smoothie or something like that but
sometimes you want something kind of
savory you know and uh I love curries so
over my years I've made a few different
banana curries and I wanted to share one
of my all-time favorite banana curries
and that's exactly what we're going to
get into thank you so much water online
this actually is what I call High
fashion banana uh kind of like the Gucci
ripoff I believe it is is it Gucci or um
another one if anyone knows what the
kind of print is a copy of let me know
but I designed it myself and I have it
in sweaters and hoodies and even jogging
pants and t-shirts and a whole bunch
more a whole bunch of fun stuff but I
got a lot of fun banana based clothing
cuz I just I just love bananas I think
they're freaking great so so if you guys
have any questions absolutely let me
know without further Ado I might as well
get into this cuz I could just talk and
talk and talk and I think you guys came
here for the food demo right and I have
another live with Rudy Eva fairly
shortly after this so going to want to
have time to eat this and then get ready
for that as well so I'm going to switch
over to the camera view hopefully this
works really well let's see oh gosh is
it not going to work for me come on
buddy you can do it come on oh I was
doing it
wrong yeah I was just doing it wrong
look at that look at that so this is the
cool thing about this Ray band meta we
can look at all the ingredients and you
can look at me chopping and all that
kind of fun stuff so I got my big bowl
over here it's a 600 G Bowl oh I'm
looking at the camera it's a 600 G bowl
and I often uh put up to like 2 and 1 12
kilos of food in there sometimes and go
crazy get in a big ass Curry but we're
going to fill this up part way this
isn't the giant giant portion but it's a
pretty good siiz portion let me know if
this is kind of a weird view for you
guys but it probably won't be once I
start chopping so here we go this is the
uh banana recipe book here big bananas
big banana book hopefully it works for
me let's see oh gosh look at that how
embarrassing there's the big banana book
and there's a lot of information in here
look at all that boom bada bing bada
boom all of that and lots of info nice
banana skateboards and banana other
banana tattoo oh my God are you serious
yeah I am look at that goes into a whole
bunch of stuff but I won't show you all
of it oh yeah see look at there there we
go I'll show you some of that there's
some of my banana clothing today there
we go look at some of the banana
clothing there and we'll just keep
scrolling oh this is going to be faster
if I do this I
think lots of different recipes gosh
look at that oh man green smoothies oh
oh ice creams and so much more oh banana
dongs oh my oh gosh I'm got to get
through all this I don't to give all of
it away do I huh I want to give away a
bunch but there we go banana Savory
banana recipe so there's the banana
Curry what it's going to look like
roughly afterwards and there's that
banana noodle Curry so I mean you could
just uh screenshot that and have it or
you could just watch this video right
you know banana peels act as an insect
bite reliever pretty cool so we have as
part of the sauce five bananas I would
like this to be a little bit riper but
uh I was last minute grabbing bananas
cuz I didn't find any ripe ones at the
market but where we're going to start is
actually with the noodles and I like to
make the sauce afterwards it's kind of
funny I always want to look here I have
a pineapple shirt and watermelon
earrings that's so fun I I love fruit
fruity kind of clothing super fun so
what we're going to do is start with
this Nappa cabbage and this is about uh
uh about a pound or 460 grams of Nappa
cabbage yeah this is through my glasses
pretty darn cool hey it's my Ray-Ban
meta so let's see hopefully this doesn't
turn it off but hello here I am but uh
the
glasses film this perspective for me
which is really fun and makes this kind
of food demoing hopefully fun this is my
first food demo ever using the rayb band
meta so let me know what you guys think
and if you have any questions but Nappa
cabbage I want to start there I
absolutely love Nappa cabbage because
Lake bananas it's available year round
it's uh inexpensive compared to other
greens often like a dollar per pound
instead of three four plus dollars per
pound it's incredibly nutritious uh it's
not like other regular cabbages it's
really tender and
uh so darn delicious and yeah per
calorie it's one of the more nutritious
ones out there too um doesn't have any
things that build up and make you really
get sick of it I've had it as one of my
staple greens for probably at least a
decade absolutely love it so let's get
into this and and what I like to do too
with all salads you know I I really
don't like to have the big salad chunks
I like to make salads into noodles so
the base of this noodle Curry is
actually going to be napa cabbage
noodles and that's one of my favorite
things about Nappa too is that it's
actually uh really compact so it's heavy
for its size so you can fit a whole
bunch in your fridge and as an extra
bonus it keeps incredibly well so I've
been known to buy cases of Napa cabbage
and keep them in my fridge and they stay
good for weeks so it just makes making
food and buying in bulk which saves a
lot of money a lot easier I lovingly
call these Napa Doodles you know how we
call uh zucchini noodles zoodles and
cucumber noodles koodles well I added a
little bit of extra flare to it and I
call these Napa Doodles so it's just
really a fun way to get in more
greens I definitely and many long-term
raw vegans that have coached people for
a long time like Dr Graham and uh drors
Rick and Karen Dena and and many others
really recommend bringing in a lot of
greens for many important reasons and
with that on average it's it's uh
recommended that most people you know
depending on their size and activity
level and stuff would be optimized by
looking at getting around a pound to 2
lbs of greens and or veggies um and or
at least fruit veggies like tomatoes
cucumbers zucchinis and stuff like that
per day on average it's not like you
know miss a day or a week here and there
even a month when the Summer's going and
the fruit is just amazing that that is
like a giant deal but uh as you get
accustomed to eating more greens you
desire them more you appreciate them
more your microbiome builds up and uh
you just feel better some people have
the mistaken kind of thought that greens
slow down detoxification when in fact
greens actually contain nutrients that
help with some of the some of the
important stages of detoxification so
without eating greens you actually don't
as efficiently detoxify and some of the
uh some of the stuff just gets
circulated back in rather than actually
going through stage two detoxification
and helping with that pretty cool little
tidbit that I learned from doctors Karen
drors Rick and Karen Dena in their
mastering raw food education course
which I absolutely highly recommend as
well it's really good so I like to cut
it like this and I lovingly call this
the bum or the heart I like the bum I
like the heart too but uh you know it's
the bum and I saved this and I'll put
that in the sauce so look at that we
have about a pound of Napa Doodles and
you know that's already a pretty decent
amount for my day but we're adding to
that I very often use this much or more
for myself but for the book I made it a
little bit less than a full huge banana
Commander serving so we got those in
there what's up next uh red cabbage now
this is a really fun one let's see if I
can switch uh
really yeah look at that that's so cool
so I love uh to freeze and thaw my
cabbage you know so red cabbage green
cabbage even napa cabbage um even
carrots shredded uh lentil Sprouts
garbanzo sprouts aduki sprouts uh even
things that are a little hardier I I
really love it with cauliflower broccoli
um mushrooms they end up being stewed a
whole bunch of different things and and
actually in my stew book I go really in
depth into that with fine-tuned
information for that but what happens is
when you freeze a vegetable the water in
it expands and it ruptures the cell wall
so when you thaw it it's already
partially broken down softened and
tastes and has the mouth feel of a
cooked food but it digests really easy
in fact easier than when it's just fresh
CU it's already partially broken down uh
it's more juicy and again it just has
that mouth feel so here we have a whole
bunch of I'll switch
back yeah there we go there we go here
we have the uh Frozen and thaw red
cabbage and look at that it's so tender
it just makes it like a oh there's a
hair in there I'm eating it myself but I
don't need that so it just makes it
really neat and and that can add a
really cool different kind of texture to
your noodle dishes or to any dishes and
and like I said I I like to do that with
uh
cauliflower making curries and stuff
like that cuz then it tastes like an
authentic Curry and sometimes I actually
make this same recipe but instead am
using uh chunks of cauliflower or
dehydrated mushrooms or stuff like that
I have a pretty robust digestive system
so it works really good for me if you're
not used to that you might want to start
with small amounts whether we're talking
about the Cabbage or cauliflower
broccoli and slowly build it up that
helps you build up the microbiome and
then you don't get super gas you know
you don't want super gas unless you want
super gas right so yeah so cool hey hey
Karen
yeah uh freeze Bel mus Game Changer
absolutely so stoked you find so too it
uh makes things a heck of a lot easier
and also less expensive because then you
can buy stuff that maybe you wouldn't
but it's cheaper and also buy in bulk
and then you can just freeze it so like
I buy big batches of stuff and then I
prep it and freeze it and then it's
ready in snap like boom you know and
whether I'm making this dish or I'm
making zucchini noodles I love to add in
these Frozen thawed red or green cabbage
or broccoli or cauliflower or pea or
anything like that or you know lentil
Sprouts it's amazing seriously so dang
good so dang good so I'm not going to
add this now and I'll tell you about
that later so we have that and that was
about 150 g and we have 1 to two carrots
you know it depends on the size of
course and we got about 150 gram of
carrots here now I like to use this
little device called a Julien peeler it
is really really nice and this is kind
of fun looking back and forth hey oh hey
hey that's working oh I love the hearts
love you too thank you thank you I love
this Julian peeler this is from Turbo
but I've used other ones and it's really
fun cuz you can make zucchinis and
carrots and daon radishes and um
cucumbers of course and almost anything
you want into noodles in a snap so I
just take this and oh I'm I'm back there
yeah okay let's go back to
this bada bing bada boom huh so we just
take this and you got to watch your
fingers but we just make it into noodles
and you really got to watch your fingers
I've cut myself with this before I'll
show you a little technique I'm not
being as Speedy as I could be but oh
gosh it's a little scary sometimes you
can take a fork and stick it in there I
didn't bring a fork so but you just lay
it down and go and turn it around and
zip it up and give her guns and I could
have done this beforehand but I wanted
to food demo this you know really wanted
to food demo it there we go there we go
and I love that center part of the
carrot and if you apply less pressure it
makes thinner noodles if you apply more
pressure it makes a little bit thicker
noodles can turn it around get some of
this action some big noodles some short
noodles all of it's all good I like it
all what do you guys think does anyone
here use a uh Julian peeler huh oh wow
we're seeing a whole bunch of comments
here let's see if I can go back it's
supposed to be telling me I think if I
tap this twice let's see oh yeah Game
Changer it doesn't work for me but I'll
learn more with this is my second time
using these for this use that kind of
peer RFS that's awesome rash Yin is
amazing she has an amazing book Korean
barbecue in the bundle and it's amazing
um you know very truthfully I don't have
gloves and it's kind of funny for me
it's like a a bit of an irk I I I feel
weird I don't I don't I don't like it
not necessarily like when using a
mandolin you're you're totally right
I'll be honest yeah with a mandolin you
want those gloves that's uh I don't like
to use mandolins they scare me to be
honest but uh rubber gloves or plastic
gloves I just can't wear them when I'm
chefing it just I need to feel the food
you know
so but um I I'm just pretty careful here
and accept if I cut myself but uh I I
think we should all just go with
whatever Comfort level we're at and
utilize whatever we need to Nate taught
us that fork to hold down is the veggies
yeah total Game Changer too yeah getting
cut is not fun it's true I'll admit I'm
kind of a bit of a lazy one and also
sometimes I like to make things more
difficult for myself for some odd reason
uh it's just my truth you know but this
works pretty darn good we got that I'm
going to put this aside cuz that'll go
in the sauce as well and we'll do this
here I'll try and do it a little bit
quicker so that I'm not just talking
about carrots for this whole time you
know cuz carrots are pretty fun high in
vitamin A you know lots of good stuff in
there and uh beta carotene you know
precursor so it's really really nice and
adds a nice different texture if you
wanted you definitely could also noodle
these like this and then freeze them and
thaw them alongside with the red cabbage
and that will make a softer carrot
noodle really really nice too I just
wanted to make it uh a little bit of a
different texture and showcase all the
different ways of doing it so we'll just
put that in there bada bing bada boom
use this awesome raw Obsession knife
from my friend Victor raw by Victor I
think is still his Instagram I'm not
sure but he recently changed the names
of the knife uh still has that symbol
and uh I'll try and Link it in in the uh
show notes afterwards cuz it's awesome
awesome knives so we got that what else
we got we got red onion so we're getting
into the actual curry sauce so I'm going
to take these guys not yet not yet we
can mix this up give it a little bit of
a mixoo look how beautiful that is it's
just so beautiful nice and fresh so some
is fresh a little bit as Frozen In tha
for different textures and flavors and
nutrients and colors and
deliciousness delicious just delicious
look at that all right so we got that
going on should we no we're not going to
we're going to start making the sauce oh
is that right in the way no it's not in
the way I was going to like oh gosh is
that in the way it's not in the way not
in the way hello everyone if you're just
joining us now uh we're doing a banana
Curry food demo banana noodle Curry from
my banana Commander big banana book yeah
yeah I want to switch back for a second
that's kind of
fun yeah little banana Curry de demo so
it's uh part of the ultimate raw vegan
bundle if you haven't heard about it yet
you probably have but if you haven't
it's live right now only until the 12th
at 11:59 p.m PST and then it's gone
forever this only happens once a year
and I need to emphasize that it's all
100% brand new books and courses never
before released no repeats if you've
ever got any other bundle none of these
are in there and it's all 100% raw vegan
lowfat oilfree ranging from simple to
more elaborate kind of raw Gourmet super
delicious and we have our group uh group
themed lowfat raw desserts ebook in
there which is completely exclusive to
this bundle after the bundle's gone it
won't be sold El elsewhere at all so
it's a Collector's Edition for each
bundle we have a completely new group
book so that's kind of neat but uh let's
get back into it and just so you know if
you get bored of me and you get sick of
this you know I have linked uh pinned in
the comments is the bundle link so you
can check that out if you want to show
me some love and support definitely
appreciate that I'll stoked you're
loving the bundle already I know you got
it that's awesome that's awesome do you
have any favorite books so far that
you've checked out there's so many good
ones
so back to here oh there we go it's like
it's like now live from your glasses
it's telling me so we're going to make
this curry sauce and again we got five
bananas that are roughly about 575 gam
that's something that's kind of
important to note if you're using
something like chronometer or fit day or
whatever something like that the
measured portion that is in there is for
the edible portion not for the skin so
this is much more it's like 900 G but
when we take that off then uh it's about
575 is you know on average four
mediumsized bananas is about a pound so
we'll just put these bananas into the
blender right here my trusty Vitamix
blender which they actually have a sale
going on right now uh Mother's Day sale
and you can get a Vitamix blender for
his low is I think 239 bucks right now I
do have an affiliate link but it's not
convenient for me to put it in the Lin
in BIO or anything like that so you can
just go straight there if you're looking
for a Vitamix and want to get a really
good deal see cabrin books yeah they're
so darn good this one's amazing I mean
raw vegan desserts most of them are high
fat so this is a fun way of getting in
more desserts but having them be lowfat
delicious and uh nutritious and you know
not superstitious at all they're uh
really really good and straightforward
so that's really fun see got the bundle
too oh bless you Mary that's awesome
thank you so much for the support I
absolutely hope you love it and I'm
confident that you will it is just
jam-packed with goodness I tell you
there's so many good books and uh all
the contributors are so amazing feel
very very blessed to be a part of this
and to be making this bundle spread out
with everyone
so let's see get that in there get that
in
[Music]
there and so we got the bananas in there
now I'm not worried about those little
banana spring strings we have some red
onion 28 G you might think like bananas
and bananas and onions are you kidding
me it's amazing it's really good and you
can admit it if you don't like uh onion
or you could use green onion or you can
use onion powder because onion powder is
a little bit milder on the system the
main thing that is kind of irritating
with onions is the mustard oil and if
you chop up your onions and let them sit
out for like 10 15 minutes then uh that
mustard oil dissipates and is a lot
milder and less irritating on the
digestive tract uh but there are really
cool things in onions and fibers in
there they are Prebiotic fibers they're
really good for the microbiome and
nutrients like sulfur which aren't super
rich in a raw food diet unless you eat
some garlic or onions or durian and
sulfur is really important for
detoxification as well onions are
another one that I love love love to
slice up and freeze and then thaw and it
makes it seriously like translucent and
Mild like cooked onions so that's
amazing in so many dish dishes I tell
you if you haven't had a frozen thought
onion Game Changer you know seriously so
damn good it's awesome so we're just
going to put this whole thing in there
and if anyone has seen uh I'm still
getting used to this if
anyone the last air bender in in that uh
in in that they say that the secret to
Enlightenment is actually banana onion
smoothies I I'm not going to claim that
at all but it's it's kind of interesting
that they mention that we got bananas
and onion so maybe this is just going to
Enlighten the heck out of us with this
ban banana noodle Curry what do you
think you know give me a heart if you
think it's going to bring instant
Enlightenment I think it might all right
so we'll also put the little bits of
this uh
carrot in
there no waste needed it'll go in there
really nice we'll also put the little
bit of the bum of this in there why not
it's delicious I don't want to cut off
my fingers live that'd be really sad I'm
getting hearts in here I love it we got
Ginger uh what do we have this says a
teaspoon or tables spoon I'm just lazy I
don't even peel it uh just throw it
right in there and then we have two
tablespoons of hemp seeds my favorite
fat I love it I love hemp seeds we're
going to put that in there and I forgot
something I completely forgot something
I am so embarrassed I can't believe it
let's see I
I'll
so fat fat and sweet fruit classic food
combining goes against fat and sweet
fruit some people are really afraid of
it uh some people talk really against it
I agree you know having 50% fat and 50%
sweet fruit like date nut bars and stuff
like that which can be really tasty and
I'm not going to like never eat those
ever but I wouldn't make stuff like that
a staple in the raw food diet it's
really hard on insulin function it's
hard on digestion um but does taste
great you know but when we're talking
about a little bit of fat with a lot of
sweet I find it digests incredibly well
a little bit slower than without the fat
but still incredibly well uh offers a
different nutrient density and a little
bit of the efas especially with the hemp
seeds they're just like a perfect a
perfect easy digesting fat with a
perfect omega3 to6 ratio and you got to
think durian it's a fatty sweet fruit
you know I enjoy the heck out of that
I'm not afraid of durian I don't make
this every single day and I don't eat
durian every single day but I'm not
afraid to mix it and have it on occasion
you know you do you you know you try it
out boo as Janette would say you know
but uh yeah give that a go I'm going to
I I forgot curry powder I forgot curry
powder oh gosh which curry powder oh
gosh oh gosh um yeah we'll use Berber oh
I forgot
ah ah I forgot we got Berber powder yeah
Berber is one of my favorite Curry
powders it's an Ethiopian uh curry
powder but really whatever curry powder
you like would
work in there we said two tablespoons I
sometimes like to make it a little bit
stronger wow dipping right in the jar
can you believe it how disgusting I'm
going to do that and this is a spicy
spicy curry powder so this will actually
be pretty pretty darn intense but
delicious as well what do you get durian
in Sweden oh you know there's a bunch of
uh there's a bunch of markets out here
Asian markets and that's probably the
best place in any major city that you
can find durian you'll find it in the
freezer section uh and also they can
have it fresh sometimes too so I can get
fresh durian I can get Frozen durian
year I can get Frozen durian year round
fresh dur in a couple months of the year
pretty expensive but look at that that's
all the sauce ingredients so we're going
to try and do something here I want to
show something off we're going to blend
this just a little bit just to get it
started hopefully I have my tamper
somewhere there you are tamper look how
messy oh gosh there's the the uh food
food uh processing component that
actually fits on this Vitamix accent
Vitamix is really awesome so I'm just
going to start it
slow sorry for the noise just going to
get it started get in there get in there
get in there get in there get in there
get in there get in there get in
there okay we're going to get that in
there like that and shake that off put
that in the bowl and I'm going to show
you a little trick that I do I'm going
take this is just like a a silicon lid
and I put a couple slits in it and I
might have to stand up to make this
easier you're seeing my view right yeah
okay good and just to make sure right
this one's a little small I actually had
some bigger ones eventually they kind of
get
wrecked I've used uh I think two of
these Lids over the last like two or
three or eight months or so but you
stretch that over top take this press it
on oh look at that did it just break
look at that it just actually broke on
me so that just shows it you know it's
not the perfect fix um but I would
otherwise be putting that on there and
uh how embarrassing I'm going to switch
for a second shame for a little
bit it just shows that it's not quite
perfect yet but I do have some extra
ones I just don't have them prepped to
do this but what that does is it creates
a perfect seal and then I
use my BIOS Chef vacuum which very sadly
apparently they aren't selling these
separate anymore and I'm going to have
to look into this more I had a whole
video already to launch about turning
your Vitamix Ascent series into a vacuum
blender do have a du d uh DIY
do-it-yourself vacuum blender with a
Vitamix video which you can check out on
my YouTube channel just like Vitamix
blender hack vacuum blender or something
like that um it doesn't use this it uses
a hand pump and it works good where I
going to do an update with this but
apparently now they don't sell them
anymore and what that allows me to do I
can switch back to
here is vacuum it and I can still do it
it's without that uh component that
these new asent series it has this lid
on it which fits perfectly with this and
then when I do that it actually creates
a vacuum seal and removes the oxygen
from the container or a bunch of the
oxygen from the container and what that
does is reduces the oxidization of the
bananas or whatever your blending in
there and it's amazing it makes it a
brighter color it makes it significantly
higher in antioxidant capacity and also
it whips less air in there because you
know there's just less air so you don't
get air bubbles in it it makes smoothies
and sauces taste more intense and uh
seriously also seem like it's more
watery it's really crazy so yeah that's
that's creating a vacuum just not quite
as good as it does with that extra seal
we're going to blend this up excuse your
ears yep I want to blend it till totally
smooth you can see those air bubbles but
with less oxygen there's less
oxidization
come on blend
blend blend come on go
now good enough good enough oh there we
go now check this out so take this off
hopefully it worked a little bit but it
works better has a better seal with that
uh that other kind of lid that just just
broke on me right so sad it's so sad but
I'll figure that
out there we go oh my gosh I wish you
could smell this I wish you could smell
this it's it's so funny for me I want to
look back and see me I kind of wish that
you could I could see me too at the same
time maybe there's a way to do that I'll
I'll look into that later but wow
yeah whoops sorry that was out a hand
wasn't it that was just oh I just hit my
elbow When It Hurt oh my gosh oh my gosh
so look got all these beautiful noodles
welcome everyone I hope you're enjoying
this give me some love if you're
enjoying this let me know if you got the
bundle and share what your favorite book
is if you haven't got the bundle yet I
don't know what you're waiting for it's
ridiculous you're going to want to check
it out I even got the link pinned in my
uh comment section here so we're just
going to pour that right in there oh my
gosh oh my gosh look at that look at
that oh oh yeah get in there get in
there this is another one of those
things where I kind of mentioned before
I like to make things harder on myself I
don't like spatulas I just don't like
using them
so yeah we all ever weird things I
accept them I I don't mind I just I
prefer to just struggle I guess you know
life's about struggle right so that's
just going to struggle you know maybe if
someone gave me a spatula a really good
one I'd use it but yeah yeah this works
good enough I can
just m o that's actually quite good
that's oh that's actually delicious oh
that's nutritious too wow that M I like
it m banana Curry so this isn't done yet
don't don't don't think that you've
learned everything everything yet just
like just hold your horses all right
just hold your horses so oh gosh pie
went out so I'm going to stir this
up oh yeah stir it right up just like
Bob Marley said right Stir It
Up darling Stir It Up There we go and
the last thing we got here oh thank you
Mary last thing we got here
is the red cabbage noodle now the only
reason I put these in last is cuz they
can kind of impart some of their
pigmentation on it and I want it to look
as nice as possible uh a little trick
that I did with this too though is I
thought it and then I squeezed it I mean
it's some of the nutrition is going to
get out of it I'll be honest and lots of
the purple um but it makes it look a
little better and since you know we're
making this as a food demo I did that
you don't have to you can just kind of
like you know kind of like use a
strainer and get most of the water out
and then dump it in but that will then
make your Curry look a little more
purple which if you don't mind a purple
Curry and you're not taking pictures of
it or you just don't care you know well
then do that right but uh we'll just
dump these in there and I'll to scoop
some of that
out but bing bada boom I'm addicted to
the bada big bada boom let's stir that
in there let's get that that beautiful
color I mean you could add more stuff to
this as you if you like but uh I figured
that most people probably would be a
little bit afraid of the concept of
banana Curry and mixing their bananas
with veggies which bananas and greens
are like a Max m match made in heaven
and uh you know look at that little
carrot just turned into a ball in there
that's so
weird but they go phenomenally well and
this was what I figured was a nice kind
of entry level banana curry without
getting super crazy oh my God look at
that but this is a inexpensive really
easy and quick super satisfying Curry
meal with sweet fruit with bananas you
know and uh I find it makes it easier to
get a bunch more calories in your dinner
meal and uh a cheaper way too to to
sometimes make it cuz sometimes tomatoes
are just bunk and not really good
quality or the mangoes aren't very good
for my Curry sauces and that's actually
what led me to making banana Curry was
just I didn't have the other red regular
ingredients for my curry sauce I'm like
I got lots of bananas let's try this
banana Curry out instead right so that
was how the banana Curry was born and
now we have the banana Curry spreading
around the world for everyone to see and
hopefully more of you enjoy this banana
noodle Curry dish I going take a bite
you know because what's a food demo
without taking a bite right do you guys
want to see the bite this way yeah
probably better this way then you can
actually see it going in my mouth
instead of just like under the glasses
that'd be really awkward wouldn't it
just hearing me chew and not even
knowing maybe I'm just putting it behind
my back like like dumping it cuz it's
disgusting and like just fooling you I
could be doing that just like tossing it
you wouldn't even know but this way you
actually know it's pretty fun it looks
pretty darn good hey it tastes even
better than it looks I I'm not even
joking it is ridiculous it is so good
this is one of my favorite curries and
uh it is a go-to for me in the winter
sometimes when like I said the mangoes
or tomatoes aren't as good I still want
something Savory don't want to just have
a banana smoothie for dinner let's go
for
it mhm
mhm pupil are bigger eyes
better I'm in love
M something just hit like push the right
button it was like bing and then
everything was like
yeah you
know I'm not going to be
rude I'm going to chew it
M trust me it's worth
it I got un ey
Toth that was so damn good you know
Gandhi
said chew your drink and drink your food
you do that almost no matter what you
eat you're going to experience way
better health in digestion but when
we're talking about salads I mean a
cellulose doesn't digest you know if you
don't chew it it's not just going to
completely magically break down that's
why might might see a leaf in your
number two right chew it up chew it up
really good enjoy every single bite this
was a real Delight I definitely enjoyed
making this with you guys thank you
everyone hey Lena um it is really darn
tasty if you're just jumping in now this
is the banana noodle Curry dish from my
big banana book The Banana Commander big
banana book one of 43 recipes in that
book all ban base with lots of banana
information dispelling myths about
bananas and giving you tips and tricks
and little known facts about bananas
that will just arm you to become part of
the banana Commander Army I'm trying
toass an army banana eaters I like it
you know I've probably eaten an average
on average 40 pounds of bananas a week
for the last 20 years as a raw vegan and
more than that before not like more
quantity but I I ate them before that as
well so I've eaten a lot of bananas the
only person I know for sure who's eaten
more bananas than me Dr Graham cuz he's
been doing it for like 40 years and he's
had bananas he used to be known as the
Banana Man actually and monoman cuz he's
all about mono meals and stuff like that
but this is awesome it's a part of the
ultimate raw vegan bundle available now
Linked In My pinned comment or in my bio
or in any of the creators bios that you
just really feel like supporting go
support them show them some love and
grab the bundle through them we got uh
over 30 people in it that are just
amazing and have contributed great great
stuff to this bundle Port of their
hearts and souls years and Decades of
experience um and Chef experience and
just love of this lifestyle and wanting
to spread it so I hope you guys check
that out if you haven't yet I hope you
check out the live sheet that's linked
in the top right hand side of the bundle
web page it shows all the different
lives are going on all week I have a
whole bunch I have another one going on
if I'm not mistaken it's in 45 minutes
but it's possible it's in 17 so uh you
know I'm going to check that in a little
bit here but while we're live here
absolutely absolutely Mary I uh you know
Lissa from raer romance and I are
actually the creators of the bundle we
came together with it uh four years ago
and ever since then I mean I'd feel like
a pretty lazy one if you know as a
Creator and I didn't even put a book in
there you know for a second this year
it's been a tough year I won't won't lie
and last year at the end was a little
tough I almost considered it I I was
actually like a little spread thin I was
almost like I don't know if I can do
it but then the banana Commander book
came out and it's like it came in the
ideas and it's just like yes this is I
can do this I can make this happen and
uh it's just a joy I'm so happy I did
and I've had great feedback and I hope
you love it and all the other resources
if anyone has any questions about the
bundle about this Curry about me about
these Ray band meta glasses whatever you
know anything I got a couple extra
minutes here it can answer and otherwise
I'm just going to get to chewing because
you saw me I chew quite a bit so it
takes a little while so I'm kind of
hoping my next live is at 1930 and 45
minutes but we'll see we'll see I'll do
a little scroll here just to see if
there's any questions that I missed and
if not then I'll go right back down to
the bottom and if anyone has any new
questions then I'll get to that last
before we clear up I can feel I have
something in my teeth it's really
bothering me thank you for the hearts
sneaky b69 and Mary G appreciate that
for
sure a stoked you love the live demos I
didn't see that before Mary I have at
least two more from book literally smell
when you open the jar it is really
potent it's really really good how do
you spell bear be bear bber berry berry
I've heard different pronunciations it
is spelled b e r b e r e b e r b e r e
bear bear yeah it's delicious oh my my
glasses disconnected but we're still
live got a live well probably don't see
it now watermelon lime thanks for
enjoying
oh oh let's see oh yeah I think uh I
think I've gone through all the
questions I'm going to go to the very
bottom now and see if there's
anything extra anything new and if not
then I'm just going to thank youall yeah
thank you all really appreciate you
coming and spending this time with me
live I hope you enjoyed the food demo
and that you try this out even if you
don't grab the bundle at least try some
of the food demos that people make
they're really delicious uh this is a
fun recipe it's easy quick to make hope
you love it hope you love all the other
ones and uh as I bid you ad do if you
haven't checked out just click that link
pinned in the comments just to check it
out oh I got a heart 100% I love it I
love it appreciate it well as always
everyone wishing you much peace love and
seasonal fruit I'll see you in the next
live in a little bit much love from my
kitchen I'm going to Chow on this see
you don't hesitate grab the ultimate raw
vegan bun now before it's gone